为什么我们会在这儿
Why were we here?
你要像个听话的小兵一样乖乖地遵从老爸的命令吗
Could you follow dad's words like a good, little soldier?
你可以不顾一切就为了得到他的认可
Are you that desperate for his approval?
这不是你的本意  萨姆
This isn't you talking, sam.
这就是你我的不同
That's the difference between you and me.
我有自己的想法  我不像你那么可悲
I have a mind of my own. I'm not pathetic like you.
老爸去世前告诉了我一些事情
Before dad died, he told me something.
他说我有可能会杀了你  萨姆
He said that I might have to kill you, sam.
-这到底是什么意思  - 我不知道
- What the hell is that supposed to mean? - I don't know.
我们在谈论科尔特  对吧
We're talking about the colt, right?
如果你仍打算那个疯狂的猎杀恶魔任务的话
If you are still set on the insane task of killing the devil,
我们就得这么做
This is how we do it.
-你们在玩LARP  对吧  - 你说什么
- You guys are larping, aren't you?  - Excuse me?
真人角色扮演
Live-action role-playing.
-你们是粉丝  - 什么粉丝
- You're fans.  - Fans of what?
卡佛·爱德兰德的《凶鬼恶灵》
"Supernatural" by carver edlund.
他叫是恰克·雪利  他是个天才
His name's chuck shurley. And he's a genius.
我是迪恩  这是萨姆
I'm dean. This is sam.
就是你书里写的那个迪恩和萨姆
The dean and sam you've been writing about.
我写下了那些东西  然后他们成真了
I write things and then they come to life.
-显然我是上帝  - 他是上帝的先知
- Obviously I'm a god. - He's a prophet of the lord.
你  你是
You. You're...
卡佛·爱德兰德  对  嗨  贝基
Carver edlund, yeah. Hi, becky.
我是你的头号粉丝
I am your number-one fan.
但我知道《凶鬼恶灵》只是一本书  对吧
But I know that "Supernatural" is just a book, okay?
-贝基  那全是真实的  - 我就知道
- Becky, it's all real. - I knew it!
你还好吗  女士
You okay, lady?
萨姆  这真的是你吗
Sam...Is it really you?
你真结实
And you're so firm. Uh...
迪恩  快点
Dean. Come on!
恰克  你在这儿
Chuck! there you are.
哥们
Guys.
发生了什么
What's going on?
没什么事
Uh, nothing.
你知道的  我只是在这儿随便走走
You know, just, um, I was kind of hangin'.
你们来这里干吗
What are you guys doing here?
你叫我们来的啊
You told us to come.
不  我没有
Uh, no, I didn't.
你有  你发消息给我的
Yeah, you did. You texted me --
这个地址  “生死攸关的情况”
This address, "life-or-death situation."
有让你想起什么吗
Any of this ringing a bell?
不  我没有给你发过消息
No, i-i-i didn't send you a text.
我们整晚都在开车
We drove all night.
我很抱歉  我不知道怎么回事
I'm sorry. I-i-i don't understand what could --
-噢 不  - 怎么了
- Oh, no.  - What?
萨姆  你来了
Sam! you made it!
贝基  对吧
Becky, right?
你还记得
Oh. You remembered.
你一直想着我的
You've been thinking about me.
我
I...
很好
It's okay.
我也没有忘记你
I can't get you out of my head, either.
你用过我的电话吗
Um, did you take my phone?
我从你的裤子里拿的  只是借用了下
I just borrowed it. From your pants.
-贝基  - 怎么了
- Becky. - What?
他们也会想要看到的
They're gonna want to see it.
-看什么  - 看什么
- See what? - See what?
噢  天哪
Oh, my god.
我爱死他们同时说话的时候了
I love it when they talk at the same time!
恰克  过来哥们  该你了
Hey, chuck! come on, pal. It's showtime.
哥们  我为这一切
Guys, I'm sorry.
说一声抱歉
For everything.
迪恩  你看上去不错嘛
Hey, dean! lookin' good!
你到底是谁啊
Who the hell are you?
我也是迪恩
I'm dean, too.
是萨姆和迪恩啊
Uh-oh. It's sam and dean.
我现在有点麻烦  你们两个玩得开心啊
I'm in trouble now. Have fun, you two.
怎么回事
What?
贝基  这是什么情况
Becky, what is this?
太棒了
It's awesome!
一个《凶鬼恶灵》粉丝会  第一次聚会
A "Supernatural" convention. The first ever.
欢迎来到第一届《凶鬼恶灵》粉丝会
Welcome to the first annual "Supernatural" convention.
屋子里有45名成员
45 in the magnolia room,
我们有专业小组
We have the panel
有5名男生组成的迪恩私生活小队
Five little boy The secret life of dean."
然后在下午的四点半
and four-thirty
有一场关于《凶鬼恶灵》的同人活动
There's the homoerotic subtext of "Supernatural."
在晚上七点我们的作者会表演节目哦
Oh,and caused big hands stars at 7:00 p.m show.
好  不过现在
Okay, but -- but right now --
现在我很高兴介绍作者本人
Right now I'd like to introduce the man himself.
《凶鬼恶灵》系列丛书的创作人
The creator and the writer of the "Supernatural" books,
他就是独一无二的
The one, the only...
卡佛·爱德兰德
Carver edlund!
好吧
Uh, okay, good.
我看上去还不是那么笨拙
This isn't nearly as awkward as I --
有点口干
It's a little dry mouth.
好吧
Okay, uh...
那么  我觉得
So, I guess, uh...
来提问吧
Questions?
你来
Um, you?
你好  爱德兰德先生  我是你的超级粉丝
Hey, mr. Edlund. Uh, big fan.
我只是想知道
Wow. Okay. I was just wondering --
你最初是怎么想出萨姆和迪恩的
Where'd you come up with sam and dean in the first place?
我
Oh, uh, i, uh...
就这么想出来了
It just...Came to me.
好吧
Okay, uh...
下一个是
Yeah, the, uh...
有钩子的那个
Hook man.
为什么在任何打斗场景里
Why, in every fight scene,
萨姆和迪恩都用他们的枪或是小刀
Sam and dean are having their gun or knife
干掉那些坏家伙
Knocked away by the bad guy?
为什么他们不用些新武器呢
Why don't they keep it on some kind of bungee?
我  我  我真的不知道
Yeah, i-i-i really don't know.
还有问题
Yeah, follow-up --
为何萨姆和迪恩看不出露比来者不善
Why can't Sam and Dean be telling that Ruby is evil?
我是说  她明显是在用道德陷阱
I mean, she is clearly manipulating Sam
来利用萨姆
Into some kind of moral lapse.
显而易见的事儿啊  不是嘛
It's obvious, nein?
如果你不喜欢这书  那你就别看  怪物
Hey! If you don't like the books, don't read 'em, fritz!
好了  好了
Okay, okay, just, uh --
没事了
Uh, okay. It's okay.
下一个问题
So, uh, so, next question.
嗯  你
Uh, uh, y-yeah, you.
在上一本书的最后
Yeah, at the end of the last book,
迪恩下地狱了
Dean goes to hell.
那接着会发生什么
So, what happens next?
事实上  据通知
Oh, w-well, there lies an announcement, a-actually.
结局很快会揭晓的
You're all gonna find out.
多亏了阔绰的斯堪的纳维亚投资商
Um, thanks to a wealthy scandinavian investor...
我们将会继续出版下一本
We're gonna start publishing again.
亲爱的上帝  太棒了
Sweet lord, yes!
我给你拿了杯冰镇黄眼
I got you a yellow-eyed cooler.
谢谢  恰克
Thanks, Chuck.
不客气
Sure.
贝基
So, Becky, uh...
我在想  你有没有
I was wondering, um, are you doing anyth--
萨姆
Oh, hi, Sam!
打扰一下
Excuse us.
给你提个醒  我们自己的烂摊子都成一堆了
In case you haven't noticed, our plates are kind of full.
寻找科尔特  猎杀恶魔
Okay? Finding the colt, hunting the devil.
我们没时间耗在这个烂地方
We don't have time for this crap!
我可没叫你来
Hey, I didn't call you.
他是说那些书  恰克
He means the books, Chuck.
为什么还要出书
Why are you publishing more books?
为了生存啊
Um, for food and shelter?
谁给你权利来写我们的生活的
Who gave you the rights to our life story?
大天使啊  我也不想的
An archangel. And I didn't want it.
好了  放弃吧  别再出书了
Well, deal's off, okay? No more books.
我们的生活不是大众消费品
Our lives are not for public consumption.
贝基  我们先离开一会儿
Uh, Becky, would you excuse us for just a second?
你们知道我是以何为生吗
Do you guys know what I do for a living?
我们知道啊  恰克
Yeah, Chuck, we know.
好吧  那告诉我好吗  我没头绪
Then, could you tell me? 'cause I don't.
我不是一个好作家
All right, I'm not a good writer,
我也没有赚大钱的本事
I've got no marketable skills,
我也不是那些东奔西走
I'm not some hero who can just hit the road
猎杀恶魔的英雄
And fight monsters, okay?
待到世界末日之前  我还得生存
Until the world ends, I got to live, all right?
我就只剩下《凶鬼恶灵》了
And the "Supernatural" books are all I've got.
你们还想要我做啥啊
What else do you want me to do?
别  伙计们  等等
No. Guys! Wait!
女士  你还好吗
Hey, lady. Hey, you okay?
-没事  - 发生了什么事
- I think so. - What happened?
-我看见了一个鬼魂  - 鬼魂
- I saw a ghost. - A ghost?
小姐  能描述一下它是什么模样吗
Ma'am, could you tell us what it looked like?
老兄  何不让成年人来解决这些问题呢
Why don't you leave this to the grown-ups, pal?
一个女人
A woman.
她穿着老式的裙子
She was in an old-fashioned dress.
很古老
Really old.
像一个女教师或别的什么
Like a schoolmarm or something.
她跟你说了什么
Did she say something to you?
好
Okay.
靠拢来  各位
Gather close, everybody,
这是一个可怕的恐怖故事
For a terrifying tale of terror!
我看见的这个鬼魂
I saw a ghost.
正是拉缇西亚·高尔的鬼魂
None other than the ghost of Leticia Gore herself!
当我在三楼
I was on the third floor when I...
LARP已经开始了吗
Ooh, the larping's started.
又搞什么飞机
The -- what is that again?
真人秀角色扮演  一个游戏
Live-action role-playing. It's a game.
这次粉丝会的节目
The convention puts it on.
他冰冷的  令我怕得要命
...Terror gripping my heart with its icy...
老爸的日记  亲爱的萨姆  迪恩
"dad's journal -- dear Sam and Dean,
这个旅馆闹鬼  你们得找到鬼魂
"this hotel is haunted. You must hunt down the ghost.
去问问目击者  找出端倪
"Interview witnesses, discover clues,
最后找到尸骨
"and find the bones.
先找到的组将获得50美元时时乐(美国牛排店)礼物卷
"First team to do so wins a $50 gift card to sizzler.
爱你们的爸爸
Love, dad."
你们俩一定获胜
You guys are so gonna win.
为什么呢  是的  列农探员  麦卡缇探员
Why, yes, agents Lennon and Mccartney,
作为这个公司的管理人员
As manager of this fine establishment,
我能确信这里确实闹鬼
I can assure you that it is indeed haunted.
这里曾经是一个孤儿院
This building was once an orphanage
由老拉缇西亚·高尔管理着
Run by mean, old Leticia Gore.
100年前的这个晚上
100 years ago this very night,
高尔老师发疯了
Miss Gore went insane
她自杀前活活杀死了四个男孩儿
And butchered four little boys Before killing herself.
传说这四个可怜的小男孩儿的魂魄
Now folks say that the souls of those poor, little boys
都被困在了这里
Are trapped here
高尔老师邪恶的灵魂在今天这个特别的日子
And that the evil spirit of miss Gore punishes them
惩  罚  他  们
To this...Very...Day.
这不就是些社区剧院的手法吗
Well, that's just about all the community theater
我忍了
I can take.
是啊  这不能再诡异了
Yeah, this cannot get any weirder.
爸说
Dad said --
万不得已我能杀了你
He said I may have to kill you.
杀我
Kill me?
到底什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
不知道
I don't know.
-我要喝点东西  - 我要喝点东西
- I need a drink.  - I need a drink.
鬼魂探测器有反应
The emf's going nuts.
我是真的  老拉缇西亚·高尔
I'm mean, old Leticia Gore.
他们把我埋在了地下室
They buried me in the basement.
你打到我了
Ow. You got me.
你应该消失才对
You're supposed to vanish.
我要怎么消失啊
How am I supposed to vanish?
好的  迪恩  5分钟后见
Yeah, okay, Dean. We'll see you in five.
不过说真的  别吃我的彩虹糖
Hey, but seriously, dude, don't eat my skittles.
救救我们
Help us.
救救我们  高尔老师不让我们玩
Help us. Miss Gore won't let us have any fun.
这也是游戏吧
This is part of the game, right?
见鬼了
Holy mother of crap!
那  确实是
That...Was --
不听话  不听话  不听话
Naughty! naughty! naughty!
你怎么样
How you doin'?
忙着呢
Busy.
哦  你今晚真可爱
Well, you sure look lovely tonight,
尤其是扮成死了的小妞
Especially for a dead chick.
老兄  这句话我今晚听17遍了
Buddy, I have heard that line 17 times tonight, okay?
而且都是穿的和你一样的人说的
And all from dudes wearing macgyver jackets.
但是你不太一样
But you seem different.
怎么不一样
How so?
你看来不会被女人吓到
Well, you don't seem scared of women.
再说最后一遍  不是我编的
For the last time, I'm not making this up, okay?
她  她就在楼上  一个真正的  活生生的鬼魂
She -- she's upstairs. A real, live, dead ghost!
失陪一下
Excuse me.
嘿  我确定那只是一个演员
Look, I'm sure it was just one of the actors.
那又是谁揍了我一顿又消失了
Who beat the crap out of me and then vanished?
你看见什么了
You saw something?
这绝不是游戏  笨蛋
Look, this isn't part of the game, jerk.
蒂姆  我要走了  你最好跟我一起离开这里
Tim, I'm getting out of here, and you should do the same.
艾历克斯 等等
Alex, wait. I --
回来
Hey! Come back!
你怎么想
What do you think?
我觉得那家伙不是装出来的
I don't think that guy's a good enough actor to be acting.
没错  扎格和理查德探员
Why, yes, agents jagger and richards,
作为这里的经理
As the manager of this fine establishment,
我负责任的告诉你们这里确实在闹鬼
I can assure you it is indeed haunted.
这个楼曾经是个孤儿院
The building was once an orphanage
由老拉缇西亚·高尔管理着
Run by mean, old Leticia Gore.
打扰一下  我们能问几个问题吗
Excuse us. Mind if we ask you a few questions?
伙计  我可没空陪你们玩星战游戏
Look, I don't have time to play "star wars," guys.
去问戴围巾那人吧
Go ask the guy in the ascot.
实际上我们
Actually, we, uh...
非常想问你
Really want to talk to you.
好吧  你们真是太投入了
Okay. You guys are really into this.
你不会了解的
You have no idea.
想知道什么
What do you want to know?
他们说的那些事
All this stuff they're saying --
闹鬼的地方 拉缇西亚·高尔
Place being haunted, Leticia Gore.
那些是真的吗
Any truth to it?
我们通常不愿意公开宣传这个
We generally don't like to publicize this
不愿意让大众知道
To, you know, normal people.
但1909年这里是高尔孤儿院的时候
But, yeah, in 1909, this place was called Gore orphanage.
高尔小姐用切肉刀杀了四个男孩
Miss gore killed four boys with a butcher knife,
然后自杀了
Then offed herself.
那么今天确实是周年纪念
And is tonight really the anniversary?
没错  我猜你们的活动需要真实感
Yep. Guess your convention folks wanted authenticity.
有过什么异常吗
There been any sightings?
前几年
Uh, over the years, yeah.
有几个女佣辞职了
A few maids have quit,
她们说听到或者见到了那些孩子
Saying they heard the boys or saw them.
一个看门人甚至看见高尔小姐了
A janitor even saw miss Gore once.
高尔小姐在哪杀的他们
Where did miss Gore carve up the kids?
我觉得你们在这到处走
Look, I don't want you stomping all over the joint.
这里很多地方是闲人免进的
A lot of this place is off-limits to nerds.
在阁楼
The attic.
鬼魂探测器抽了
The emf's going nuts.
很好
Great.
确实有个鬼
So, we got a real ghost,
还有一堆傻帽装成咱们俩在找
And a bunch of dudes, pretending to be us, poking at it.
简直是胡来
No way this ends well.
你知道吗  他们活该
You know what? Serves them right.
迪恩
Dean.
我说说而已
Well, I'm just saying.
就是这附近动某个地方了
It's got to be around here someplace.
我不知道哎
Yeah, I don't know, man.
没别人在找阁楼了
No one else is looking for the attic.
好吧  兄弟
Okay, all right, dude.
首先  进入角色  行不
One, stay in character, all right?
只有我当真的话  看起来很傻
If it's just me, I look stupid.
第二  你听见楼下那人说的了
And, two, you heard the guy downstairs.
我觉得这是游戏的一部分
I think this is part of the game.
帮帮我们
Help us.
哦  我的天哪
Oh, my god!
妆画得太好了
That makeup is amazing.
你这外行
Amateur.
注意  你的  角色
Stay...In...Character.
抱歉  抱歉
Sorry. Sorry.
帮帮我们  高尔小姐不让我们玩
Help us. Miss Gore won't let us have any fun.
尸体埋在哪了  孩子
Where's the body buried, kid?
我们会把她彻彻底底的烧掉
We'll light her up nice and toasty.
没错
Yeah.
跑的真快
Wow. Fast runner.
兄弟
Dude.
看看那个
Check this out.
哦  真恐怖
Oh, that is creepy.
要按他说的做吗
Must've been what he was trying to tell us.
你觉得呢  萨姆
Gee, you think, sammy?
好吧  这是我见过的最酷的游戏
Okay, this is the coolest game ever.
是的
Yes.
我妈妈爱我
My mommy loves me.
我说我妈妈爱我
I said my mommy loves me.
我相信她爱你
I'm sure she does.
我妈妈就这么爱我
My mommy loves me this much.
真可怕
Awesome.
好吧  那
All right, so...
这是个本地历史上提到的家伙
That was a guy with the county historical society.
还有呢
And?
拉缇西亚·高尔不但杀了四个男孩
Not only did Leticia Gore butcher four boys,
而且其中之一是她的儿子
But one of them was her own son.
-她儿子  - 没错
- Her son? - Yeah.
根据警察的记录
According to the police at the time,
她扒了那孩子的头皮
She scalped the poor kid.
哦  我要油炸了这抽风的贱人
Oh, that's it. I'm gonna deep-fry this bitch extra-crispy.
-知道她埋在哪吗  - 他不知道
- Dude say where she was buried? - He doesn't know.
看这个
Check it out.
那儿是孤儿院  这儿是马车棚
There's the orphanage, here's the carriage house.
那儿  就是墓地
And right there, cemetery.
你觉得拉缇西亚埋在那儿吗
You think that's where Leticia's planted?
值得去看看
It's worth a shot.
嘿  嘿  这是我的
Hey. Ooh. Hey, hey! hey, do you mind?
这是真的  至少一个世纪以前的纸
It's real. A century old, at least.
他是对的  墓地就在外面
And he's right. There is a cemetery on the grounds.
这玩意儿哪来的
Where'd you get that?
这叫游戏  朋友
It's called a game, pal.
不是慈善捐助
It ain't called "charity."
好吧  把地图给我  笨蛋
All right, give me the map, chuckles.
你们才是笨蛋呢
Oh, you're the chuckles...
笨蛋们
Chuckles.
还有  迪恩谁的话都不会听的
Besides, Dean don't listen to nobody.
迪恩  冷静点
Dean...Cool it.
迪恩
Dean.
什么  他们烦死了
What? They're friggin' annoying.
听着  伙计们  我们都想找到骨头  对吧
Look, guys, we all want to find the bones, right?
我只是想  大家合作会快一点
We just thought it would go faster if we all work together.
时时乐的礼物卷归我们
We, uh, we get the sizzler gift card.
好吧
Fine.
萨姆和迪恩的称号也归我们
And we get to be Sam and Dean.
好吧
Fine.
真好
Yes.
嘿  鲁佛斯  鲍比  快一点
Hey, Rufus, Bobby, would you hurry it up?
你还好吧
You alright?
我尽量
I'm trying to be.
我们刚才在哪里
So, where were we?
艾利卡特医生刚把你杀了
Uh, dr. Ellicott had just zapped your brain.
是的  知道啦
Right. Got it.
迪恩 我们为什么还要来这里
Why are we even here, Dean?
你不是只要跟随父亲的脚步
Do you just follow in dad's footsteps
就像一个优秀的小兵
Like a good, little soldier?
你就那么想得到认可
Are you that desperate for approval?
萨姆 这不是你的本意
This isn't you talking, Sam.
这就是你我的区别
See, that's the difference between you and me.
我有自己的想法  我不是可怜虫
I got a mind of my own. I'm not pathetic.
那你想怎么做 萨姆 杀了我
So, what are you gonna do, Sam? You gonna kill me?
伙计  我讨厌你告诉我做什么
Man, I am so sick of you telling me what to do!
够  我受够了
Oh, you know what? That -- that's it.
够了
That is it.
怎么了  鲍比
What's wrong, Bobby?
我不是鲍比
I'm not Bobby, okay?
你不是萨姆
You're not Sam.
你也不是迪恩
You're not Dean!
你们有毛病吗
What is wrong with you?
你们到底为什么想当他们
Why in the hell would you choose to be these guys?
我们是粉丝啊  就像你们一样
Because we're fans, like you.
不
No.
我不是粉丝  好吧  不是
I am not a fan, okay? Not fans.
说实话  我觉得迪恩和萨姆的故事烂透了
In fact, I think that the "Dean and Sam" story sucks!
不好玩也没乐趣
It is not fun. It's not entertaining.
这个故事糟透了
It is a river of crap
会把大多数人送进精神病院
That would send most people howling to the nuthouse!
听我说
So, you listen to me.
他们的痛苦不是你们的消遣
Their pain is not for your amusement.
我是说  你们认为
I mean, do you think that they enjoy
他们想被当成马戏团小丑吗
Being treated like -- like circus freaks?
我想他们不会在意的
Uh, I don't think they care,
因为他们是虚构的人物
Because they're fictional characters.
他们在意
Oh, they care.
相信我
Believe me.
他们非常在意
They care a lot.
他
He, uh...
他把这个故事当真了
He takes the story really seriously.
-找到那4个男孩  - 这是拉缇西亚·高尔的墓地
- Found the four boys.  - And here's Leticia Gore.
你们在做什么
Uh, what are you guys doing?
我们在找尸骨 天才
Uh, we're looking for bones, genius.
他们应该在这附近
They got to be around here somewhere.
一般来说  尸骨是埋在地里的
Okay, generally, bones are in the ground.
是的
Yeah.
我知道  我只是
I know that. I'm just --
等下
Wait. Hold on.
-你们真要这么做  - 是的
- Are you guys serious? - Deadly.
我们不会真的挖墓  伙计
We're -- we're not really digging up graves, you guys.
我们只是在玩游戏  所以
We're just playing the game, so --
相信我们
Trust us.
你想赢  对吧
You want to win the game, right?
这不是塑料的尸骨
That's, uh, not a plastic skeleton.
这是真的尸骨
That's a skeleton skeleton.
你们挖的是真的墓
You just dug up a real grave.
是的
Yeah.
你们是疯子
You guys are nuts.
我记得你们说过想当猎人
I thought you said you guys wanted to be hunters.
伙计  猎人不是真实的
Hunters aren't real, man.
-这不是真的  - 上帝啊
- This isn't real.  - Oh, my god.
你们彻底迷失方向抓住这点牢牢不放了
You guys have just seriously lost your grip on this --
什么
What?
淘气  淘气  淘气
Naughty! naughty! naughty!
巴恩斯
Barnes!
上帝啊
Oh, my god!
淘气  淘气  淘气
Naughty! naughty! naughty!
够真实的了吧
Real enough for you?
那个
That was...
真是
Really...
吓人  是吧  就是这样
Awful, right? Exactly.
我们请
Round's on us, guys.
等会见
See you around.
你们怎么知道要这样做的
Hey. How did you know how to do all that?
我们
We, um...
我们读了书
We read the books.
恰克
Hey, Chuck.
祝《凶鬼恶灵》大卖
Good luck with the "Supernatural" books.
去你妈的
And screw you very much.
你的粉丝
Fans of yours?
我得说不是
Hmm. I'd say no.
很奇怪
That's weird.
绝对是
Definitely.
发现什么了
Anything?
每个出口都被锁了  貌似
Every exit's locked. Almost like...
-有什么东西不让我们出去  - 是
- Something's keeping us in? - Yeah.
太糟了
This is bad.
哎呀  你认为呢
Gee, you think, sammy?
不要到那里面去
Don't go in there!
下楼去  去  去
Get downstairs, okay? Go. Go!
你为什么要那样做
Why'd you do that?
为什么送走我妈妈
Why did you send my mommy away?
也许是因为她给你剃的锅盖头(指头上的伤)
Uh, maybe because of the high-and-tight she gave you.
怎么不感谢我们
Yeah? How 'bout some thanks?
我只是说
Well, I'm just saying,
偶尔来点感谢就可以了
A little gratitude might be nice once in a while.
妈妈没有这样对我
My mommy didn't do this to me.
什么  那么是谁干的
What? Then, who did?
多原汁原味啊
Yeah. How original.
《凶鬼恶灵》带给你更多的诡异儿童
"Supernatural" bringing you more creepy children.
可悲啊
Sigh.
高尔小姐不让我们玩
Miss Gore wouldn't let us have any fun.
你们看上去可一点都不像真的鬼
You look nothing like real ghosts.
就这么告诉你们了
Just telling you.
可是高尔小姐已经走了
But miss gore's gone,
那么现在我们可以尽情享乐了
And now we can have all kinds of fun.
我的天啊
Gott im himmel!
好吧  伙计们  我猜我们要接近尾声了
Well, guys, I guess we're -- we're out of time.
谢谢你们难以置信
So thank you for your incredibly
深入并且缜密的问题
Probing and rigorous questions,
祝你们有个愉快的
And have a good --
什么  我靠
What?! holy crap!
你必须保证这里人的安全  恰克
You got to keep everyone safe in here, chuck.
这可是生死攸关的事儿
This is life-or-death.
要多久
For how long?
需要多久就多久
As long as it takes.
可我该咋办呢
Well, how the hell am I supposed to do that?
我也不知道啊哥们儿
I don't know, man.
做就对了
Just do it.
好吧
Okay, so, uh...
好消息
Good news.
我还有更多要告诉大家的
Uh, I got much more to tell you...I guess.
太棒了
Awesome.
哥们儿  我还有工作要做啊
Buddy, I got work to do.
你绝对想看看这个  相信我
You're gonna want to see this. Trust me.
这演讲绝对酷毙了
It's gonna be a hell of a show, huh?
来吧来吧
Here we go. Here we go.
当然了  也有很多不错的女巫的
Certainly, there are a lot of nice witches, too.
萨姆和迪恩的命运会如何呢
Uh, what does the future hold for sam and dean?
好吧  你们觉得天使咋样
Well, uh, how do you feel about angels?
是啊  我跟你们说
Yeah, you know, because, let me tell you,
他们可一点都不像你们想的那么弱
They're not nearly as lame as you think.
好吧  最新消息
Okay, new theory.
关于拉缇西亚的传说明显是搞错了
The legends about leticia are ass-backwards, obviously.
好吧  我们假设那三个孤儿
Yeah, so, all right, let's say those three orphans
是在  是在玩西部牛仔和印第安人的游戏
Were -- were playing cowboys and indians.
是在角色扮演牛仔和印第安人
Larping as cowboys and indians.
随便吧  然后他们剥去了拉缇西亚儿子的头皮
Whatever -- and let's say they scalped leticia's son
然后杀了他
And killed him.
妈妈把他们当场抓获  接着她就发疯了
Mom catches them in the act, flips out,
把他们切成片  又把自己了解了
Slices them, and dices herself.
如果这是真的  那意味着
If that's true, it means
这楼里面就有三个嗜杀贪玩的小孩
We got three bloodthirsty brats in the building.
没错  在我们除掉她之前
Yeah, and leticia was the only
拉缇西亚是唯一一个
One keeping them under control.
可以管得住他们的人
Until we took her out.
我们不能打草惊蛇
Smooth move on our part.
-好的  - 我们得回到墓地去
- All right. - Well, we got to get back to the cemetery
然后烧了那些小孩的骨头
And torch the kids' bones.
怎么去  我们可被困住了
How? We're trapped.
我们连枪都没有
We don't even have our guns.
那些鬼魂在房子里到处乱窜
The ghosts are running this joint,
而且他们只怕一样东西
And they were only scared of one thing.
正解
Exactly.
你想让我干啥
You want me to do what?
你是个演员啊  我们只是想让你演演戏
You're an actress, okay? We just want you to act.
我在托莱多的猫头鹰餐厅工作
I work at hooters in toledo.
你想都别想
You can forget it.
你绝对安全  我们保证
You'll be safe. We promise.
但是这真的很重要
But this is really important.
我们想帮你们忙
We want to help.
给她点容易的事儿干  好吗
Just give her the puppy-dog thing, okay?
伙计们  不行
Guys, no.
为啥不行
Why not?
因为这可不是假的
Because this isn't make-believe.
我们知道  我们不是疯子
Look, we know. We're not nuts.
我们也怕的要死
We're freakin' terrified.
没错  但是如果这些人真的有麻烦了
Yeah, but if all these people are seriously in trouble,
我们必须做点什么
We got to do something.
为啥
Why?
因为
Because...
萨姆和迪恩会这么做
That's what sam and dean would do.
噢不  并没有什么
Uh, no, there's really no such thing
像是Croatoan病毒一样的东西
As a croatoan virus for, you know, down there.
你真该去看看医生了
You really should see a doctor.
我  我真不想这么做
I-i don't want to do this.
我就在这儿  小甜心  我会罩着你
I'm right here, sweetheart. I got your back.
相信我  这绝对有效
Trust me. This is gonna work.
男孩们
Boys!
过来  马上
Come here, this instant!
我叫你们的时候你们就得过来
You come when I call you!
明白了吗
Do you understand me?!
高尔小姐
Miss gore?
快推
Push.
你们这些男孩
You boys...
实在太淘气了
Have been very naughty.
现在  你们把门打开
Now, you open the doors.
马上把门打开
Open the doors right now!
继续继续继续
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
继续
Go!
你们都太淘气了  听见了吗
You're very naughty. You hear me?
淘气  淘气  淘气
Naughty, naughty, naughty.
该死
Ugh! damn it!
快跑
Run.
我的天
Oh, my god.
凶鬼恶灵让挖墓地
"Supernatural" makes digging graves...
变得如此容易
Seem so easy.
但完全不是这样
It's not, though.
我要放弃了
I'm gonna throw up.
不行
No, you're not.
谢了
Thanks.
萨姆
Sam!
我们看看  还有啥别的不
Let's see. Uh, what else?
我的初恋在16岁
I fell in love for the first time at 16.
事实上也失去了处子之身
Lost my virginity, actually.
但是她却到处告诉别人
But then she went around telling
那并不算数  所以
Everybody it didn't count, so...
这比较搞笑
That's kind of funny.
不好意思
Uh...Excuse me!
你  你不能走
Y-you really can't leave.
拜托了先生
Please, sir.
别去开门
Don't open that door!
我说了谁都不能出去  该死
I said no one leaves, damn it!
现在  谁来这门口撒点盐
Now, somebody salt this door!
为啥迪恩每次都能一次
How come dean can always light
就点着这白痴一样东西
This stupid thing on the first freakin' try?!
快啊
Come on!
迪恩
Dean!
或许那家伙说的没错
May be that guy is right.
也许我们也该换换新武器
Maybe we should put these things on a bungee.
我不得不感谢你们
And I got to hand it to you, guys.
那时多亏你们救了我们的小命
You really saved our asses back there.
所以
So, uh, you know...
多谢你们
Thanks.
我的天  我还不知道你们的名字呢
Gosh, I don't even know your names.
我是巴恩斯
Oh. Well, I'm Barnes.
他是德米安
This is Demian.
你呢
What's yours?
迪恩  真正的迪恩
Dean. The real Dean.
哦哟  才怪
Yeah, right!
-那我也是  - 开什么玩笑呀  迪恩
- Me too! - Get the hell out of here, Dean.
不管怎样  还是多谢
Well, anyway, uh, thanks.
真的很感谢
Really.
知道吗  其实你错了
You're wrong, you know.
你说什么
Sorry?
关于"凶鬼恶灵"的故事
About "Supernatural."
无意冒犯
No offense,
只是我觉得你并没有理解故事的精髓
But I'm not sure you get what the story's about.
是那样吗
Is that so?
是这样的  现实生活中
All right, look, in real life,
他卖音响设备
He sells stereo equipment,
而我是修复印机的
I fix copiers.
我们的生活糟糕透顶
Our lives suck.
但是作为萨姆和迪恩
But to be sam and dean...
每天早上醒来  去拯救世界
To wake up every morning and save the world...
身边有能与你同生共死的兄弟陪伴
To have a brother who would die for you...
这难道不令人羡慕吗
Well, who wouldn't want that?
或许你是对的
Maybe you got a point.
要知道  你俩合作的也不赖嘛
Well, you know, you two don't make a bad team yourselves.
你们怎么认识的啊
How do you know each other, anyway?
我们在网上认识
Oh, uh, well, we met online.
"凶鬼恶灵"聊天室
"Supernatural" chat room.
离开父母的小巢出去交点朋友
Well, it must be nice to get out of your parents' basement
真很好啊
And make some friends.
我们不止是朋友
We're more than friends.
我们是伴侣
We're partners.
好吧
Well...
好啊  情侣
Howdy, partners.
你也好
Howdy.
萨姆
Look, Sam...
我不想骗你
I'm not gonna lie.
不可否认  我俩有感觉
We had undeniable chemistry.
但就像猴子在太阳上  太热了而不能生存下去
But like a monkey on the sun, it was too hot to live.
不能再这样下去
It can't go on.
恰克和我之间彼此相识
Chuck and I -- we found each other.
我为他的英勇刚强所吸引
My yin to his proud yang.
我已心有所属
And, well, the heart wants what the heart wants.
我非常抱歉
I am so, so sorry.
是啊  萨姆
Yeah, Sam.
很抱歉
You know, sorry.
你不会有事吧
Will you be all right?
说实话  我也不知道
Honestly, I don't know.
只是我想我必须
I'll just have to --
另寻他法  继续生活下去
To find a way to keep living, I guess.
愿上帝保佑你
God bless you.
好了  恰克
Okay, um, oh, hey, Chuck,
如果你真想再出版新书
Look, if you really want to publish more books,
我们大概也没什么意见
I guess that's okay with us.
真的吗
Wow. Really?
当然不  我们有枪  会追你到天涯海角
No, not really. We have guns, and we'll find you.
好吧
Okay, okay.
不会再出书了
No more books.
回头见
See you around.
等等  萨姆  还有件事
Sam! wait! one more thing!
《凶鬼恶灵》第三章  "时间为证"
Chapter 3 in "Supernatural - Time is on my side,"
那个叫贝拉的女孩
There was that girl bela.
她是个英国飞贼
She was british and a cat burglar.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
她从你们这里偷走了Colt
She stole the Colt from you,
她还声称把科尔特交给了莉莉丝  记得吗
And then she "said" she gave it to lilith, remember?
没错
Yeah.
你知道她在撒谎吧
Well, you know she lied, right?
她从没把科尔特给莉莉丝
She never really gave it to lilith.
等等  你说什么
Wait, what?
你没看书吗
Didn't you read the book?
的确有这么一个场景
There was this one scene
贝拉把那把枪给了一个叫克罗力的恶魔
Where bela gives the colt to a demon named Crowley,
莉莉丝的得力助手
Lilith's right-hand man --
我想大概也是她的情人
I think her lover, too.
克劳力
Crowley?
你怎么之前没想到要告诉我们
Didn't occur to you to tell us this before?
抱歉  我不记得了
I'm sorry. I didn't remember.
我不像她那样痴迷
I'm not as big of a fan as she is.
贝基
Becky...
把来龙去脉都告诉我
Tell me everything.
你还好吧
You okay?
你猜怎样
Yeah, you know.
我想我棒极了
I think I'm good.
你会觉得难以置信
Well, you're not gonna believe it,
我找到了关于科尔特的线索
But I got a lead on the colt.
什么
What?
说来话长  路上慢慢说吧
Long story. Tell you on the way?
那咱们还等什么
What are we waiting for?
和大多数作家一样
Like a lot of authors,
我是因为爱而开始写作生涯的
I started writing because of love.
南希·麦积翁给了我巨大的打击
Yeah, I had a huge crush on nancy mckeon,
她在"生活的真相"这一集中饰演乔
Who played Jo on "the facts of life."
我给她写了四五十封信
I must have written her like 40 to 50 letters.
她从没回过信
She never wrote back.
我觉得食人怪没有换上
I don't think the benders made flesh suits
所有受害者的人皮
Out of all their victims, so...
最多只是用了情侣围巾的材料而已
Maybe just like a couple scarves.
其实我最爱的电影是《海滩》（1988年电影）
Actually, my favorite movie was "beaches".
希拉里和C.C真是
Hillary and C.C. Were just...
太勇敢了
So brave.
如此坚强
So strong.
我觉得吧
The way I look at it,
如果你不打算来个大改变
It's really not jumping the shark
那就不算重大转型
If you never come back down, you know?